<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>cTiVo Updates</title>
        <link>http://ctivo.googlecode.com/files/sparklecast.xml</link>
        <description>Version 2.2 (Addresses users having trouble with MAK key entry)</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>Version 2.2 (Addresses users having trouble with MAK key entry)</title>
			<description><![CDATA[
                <b>Version 2.2 (Addresses users having trouble with MAK key entry)</b><br /><br />
				<ul>
				<li>Improved handling of initial MAK entry</li>
                <li>Users can now enable and disable any TiVo with the TiVo preferences UI</li>
                </ul>
                <br />
				<b>Version 2.1 (More Major new features and UI improvements)</b><br /><br />
				<ul>
				<li>cTiVo now automatically configures an optimum workflow based on user selections so that the simultaneous encoding selection by the user is no longer necessary</li>
				<li>Commercials can now be marked as chapters on mp4 files regardless of the capability of the encoder.</li>
				<li>Subtitles are now embedded in the video file for mp4 including advanced formatting and glyphs</li>
				<li>Improved elGato support</li>
				<li>Improved UI for specification of tmp directory in Advanced Preferences</li>
				<li>Greatly improved logging for debugging support</li>
				<li>Update to HandbrakeCLI 0.99</li>
				<li>Greatly improved subscription handling including in multiple TiVo settings.  Users have the ability to specify TiVo or quality preference.  Users can also specify All to subscribe to all shows being recorded.</li>
				<li>Improved support for artwork</li>
				<li>Improved handing of Manual TiVo network access</li>
				<li>cTiVo now accesses TheTVDB.com to try to find missing episode/season information and missing artwork.</li>
				<li>Improved speed through added buffering of TiVo information</li>
				<li>Main window now allows the user to adjust window sizes</li>
				<li>Added robustness against certain TiVo network issues</li>
				<li>Many other bug fixes and UI enhancements</li>
				<li>cTiVo is now code-signed for additional security.</li>
				</ul>
                <br />
                
				
				See <a href="https://github.com/dscottbuch/cTiVo/wiki"> cTiVo Home </a> for more informaton.
                
            ]]>
			</description>
            <pubDate>Mon., Apr 8, 2013 10:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <!-- <sparkle:releaseNotesLink>http://andymatuschak.org/files/notes.html</sparkle:releaseNotesLink> -->
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/dscottbuch/cTiVo/releases/download/v2.2.451/cTiVo_2.2.451.zip"
            sparkle:version="451" sparkle:shortVersionString="2.2"
            length="16755956"
            type="application/octet-stream"
            sparkle:dsaSignature="MC0CFAzammomyeYz0FdDbhita99ZYVlVAhUAwAz2Xn/2posuRLtgEe2dQi1mrIE=" />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>

